祝贺你，你完成了课程。
Congratulations, you completed the course.
太棒了。
That's so great.
That's so awesome.
太棒了。
That's absolutely terrific.
我希望你喜欢这门课程，就像我当然喜欢创建这门课程以及我们可以用ChatGPT做的所有事情一样。
I hope you enjoy the course as much as I certainly enjoyed creating the course and all the things that we can do with ChatGPT.
因此，我将给您留下四个行动步骤，您可以立即开始实施，另外还有一个额外的步骤，我希望您也能看看。
And so I'm going to leave you with four action steps that you can take right now to start implementing this right away, plus an extra step that I'd like you to take a look at as well.
因此，第一步就是根据需要检查零件。
So the first step is just review the parts as needed.
聊天GPT中有没有一部分真的吸引了你的眼球，或者你想多回顾一下这一部分？
Was there a part of chat GPT that really kind of caught your eye or you want to review that part a little bit more?
回去看那些具体的课程。
Go back and watch those specific lessons.
继续复习，尽可能多地复习，看看那些具体的部分。
Go ahead and review it as much as you need and take a look at those specific parts.
接下来，当然要注册聊天GPT，对吧？
Next is, well, certainly sign up for chat GPT, right?
只需登录、登录、注册，然后玩它。
Just go in, log in, sign up, and then play around with it.
不要，我给了你一些想法，我用了一些技巧，一些最佳实践，无论是询问结婚信息，还是把事情放在要点上，无论是什么。
Don't, I've given you some ideas, I've used some tips, some best practices, whether it's asking for a marry information, putting things in bullet points, whatever it might be.
但你自己进去玩吧。
but go in and play around with it yourself.
这真的是最好的学习方式，也是它如何真正帮助你、发挥作用、在你的工作生活中尝试不同的事情，尤其是在你的职业生活中，这门课程围绕着你的职业生涯，但我们也有一些个人的东西。
That's really the best way to learn and how it can really help you and play around with it and try different things both in your work life and particularly your work life as this course around your work life but we've had some personal stuff too.
我们在创作音乐和诗歌方面玩得很开心。
We made some fun making music and poetry.
我们甚至从我妻子那里得到了一份很好的小礼物，正如我们在个人部分看到的那样。
We even got a nice little gift from my wife too as we saw in the personal section.
所以，用你自己、你的工作和你的个人生活来玩吧。
So play around with it with your own self and both your work and your personal life too as well.
然后真正开始，你知道，花点时间，去喝杯咖啡，放下电脑，然后思考聊天GPT如何帮助你。
And then really start, you know, take a moment, you know, go get a cup of coffee, put the computer down, and then think about how chat GPT can help you.
它在哪里可以帮助你获得最大的结果，最大的投资回报，制定一个关于你可能想通过聊天GPT利用什么的计划，以及如何将其作为你整体生活计划的一部分，无论你的工作生活计划或生活计划是什么，以及如何
Where can it maybe help you give you the biggest results, your biggest return on your investment time, develop a plan about what you might want to leverage with chat GPT and how that can be part of your overall life plan where it's part of your work life plan or your life plan, whatever your plans are around that and how it can maybe
在工作中，在你的事业中，或者如果你有副业，甚至可能在你的个人生活中，对你产生影响。
make an impact for you in work, in your business, or if you've got a side gig, or maybe even in your personal life too.
但要想一想它能对你有什么帮助。
But really think about how it can help you.
最后，第四，在额外的一步之前，一定要考虑继续你的教育。
And then lastly, number four before the extra step is do think about continuing your education.
人工智能正在发生很多事情，而且它将继续快速发展。
There's a lot going on with artificial intelligence, and it's going to keep evolving very quickly.
所以继续你对大信徒的教育，继续你的教育，不断学习。
So continue your education on Big Believer, continue your education, and continuously learning.
事实上，我在Udemy上有很多课程，所以如果你想为我修另一门课程，最简单的方法就是键入Steve Ballinger，或者实际上是Autofill，但只需在Udemi搜索栏中键入我的全名，我所有的课程都会出现。
In fact, I have a lot of courses on Udemy, so if you'd like to take another course for me, easiest thing to do is just type Steve Ballinger, or Autofill actually, but just type my full name into the Udemy search bar and all my courses will come up.
我有一些关于商业课程的课程，比如领导力和管理。
And I have courses around business courses, like around leadership and management.
我从事管理工作超过25年，许多高管理和生产力类型的课程帮助我在工作中越来越好。
I was in management for over 25 years, a lot of high management and productivity type courses helped me better and better at work.
此外，我对投资也充满热情，这让我可以提前退休，去某个地方，退休并以类似的风格创建Udemy感兴趣的课程，
And then also I have a passion around investing, allowed me to retire early, be somewhere, retire and create Udemy courses of interest in like style,
股票、债券、加密货币、房地产，不管是什么。
stocks or bonds or cryptocurrency, real estate, whatever it is.
我有很多不同的投资课程可以帮助你。
I've got a lot of different investing courses can help you there as well.
很想在另一个课程中看到，只需在Udemy搜索中键入我的名字即可搜索我。
Love to see in another course, just search for me by typing my name into the Udemy search.
然后，作为一名额外的工作人员，或者可能是我和其他学生的一个更大的帮助，嘿，请留下评论。
And then as an extra staff or maybe more of a favor from me and other students, hey, please leave a review.
转到顶部的标签，上面写着评分，然后留下对课程的回顾。
Go to the tab at the top where it says rating and leave a review of the course.
你可以留言，如果你想或只是留下一个星级。
You can leave a message if you want or just leave a star rating.
那太好了。
That would be great.
我真的很感激。
I'd really appreciate it.
请稍等片刻，留下星级评价或评论评价。
Do take a moment and leave a star rating or leave a review rating.
如果你能做到那就太好了。
That would be wonderful if you could do that.
最后结束课程，完成整个课程。
And then lastly to wrap up the course complete the whole course.
我最后想对你说声谢谢。
My last thought for you is I just want to say thank you.
非常感谢你花时间和我一起学习这门课程。
Thank you so much for spending the time with me on this course.
正如我所说，我很喜欢做这道菜。
As I said, I enjoyed making this course.
希望你也喜欢。
Hopefully you enjoyed it as well.
当然，也要想想GPT聊天可以帮助自己或帮助你的方式。
And certainly think about the ways that chat GPT can help yourself or help you.
但我只想在课程结束时说声谢谢。
But I just want to wrap up the course by saying thank you.
非常感谢。
Thank you so much.
我祝大家好运。
And I wish you all the very best of luck.